{"data":[{"question":"\"If you don't take any exercises, you won't be healthy\" - the doctor to me.     -> The doctor warned me ........................................\n","answer":"if I didn't take any exercises, I wouldn't be healthy","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"4"},{"question":"\"I'm afraid it's going to rain\" - said Dolly.     -> Dolly told me .............................\n","answer":"she was afraid it was going to rain","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"4"},{"question":"Philip in his letter: \"My hotel room here isn't very nice and I'll have to look for a better one.\"     -> Philip wrote me that ............................................look for a better one.\n","answer":"his hotel room wasn't very nice and he would have to","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"4"},{"question":"The teacher to me: \"You've failed. There are too many mistakes in your composition.\"     -> The teacher informed me .........................................................\n","answer":"I had failed. There were too many mistakes in my composition","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"4"},{"question":"\"The girls that I work with gave me a huge teddy-bear for my birthday\" - Ann said.     -> Ann said ........................................................\n","answer":"the girls she worked with had given her a huge teddy-bea for her birthday","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"4"},{"question":"\"The clock that I bought here yesterday, doesn't work\" - said the woman.     -> The woman complained that ........................................\n","answer":"the clock she had bought there the previous day, didn't work","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"4"},{"question":"\"They're playing a lot of music that I don't like\" - said the girl.     -> The girl said ................................................\n","answer":"they were playing a lot of music that she didn't like","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"4"},{"question":"\"We've been waiting for Julie for two hours and she hasn't come\" - they told us.     -> They complained that ...................................................\n","answer":"they had been waiting for Julie for two hours and she hadn't come","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"4"},{"question":"The girl to the dressmaker: \"You will have to shorten this dress for me.\"     -> The girl told the .........................................................\n","answer":"dressmaker that she would have to shorten that dress for her","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"4"},{"question":"\"I need to be at work early this morning that's why I'm in a hurry'' - said Donald.     -> Donald explained ....................................................\n","answer":"he needed to be at work early that morning that's why he was in a hurry","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"4"}]}